Tim: Um, I think to an extent you are always going to be influenced
by the way you were brought up yourself.
Tim: Um, for example, my younger children are part of the digital age,
and so it’s always a little bit of a tussle, a fight with them, to get them off screens.
Tim: And with my 27-year-old and my 29-year-old, there were screens,
but they weren’t that interesting and they weren’t on
– they didn’t want to be on them the whole time.
Syinat: Well, so, for example, my mother, when we were growing up,
she always tried to make me see us as equals in, in the relationship and so,
I definitely plan on doing that with my children as well.
Syinat: …and so, I definitely plan on doing that with my children as well…
even if that is more of a positive thing.
Devika: So, myself and, um, people of my generation were brought up in quite strict households…
Devika: …and it’s been interesting, actually, to see, for example,
one of my cousins is bringing up their children in a very different way, …